If you were to make a new structure for the next generation of 18-year-olds that would replace college, what would it look like?
I actually think what Joel Lineman is doing with Alpha School is really the much better version of what education should look like,
which is two hours a day of kind of quote formal study, which is AI tutor driven, which is learning based on the style of learning of the human.
And then six hours a day of kind of real life skills and social skills, which are far more applicable.
And even in those two hours a day, they advance at twice the speed at 98th percentile.
And so it's just like the old system is broken.
Joel Lineman, thankfully, is a multi-billionaire and like has the resources and horsepower to actually like affect change.
Many people have tried to tackle education.
Few people have succeeded, mostly because education is such an entrenched government backed blah, blah, blah.
But yeah, for 18-year-olds, I think I would more or less model that.
And a lot of learning comes from eliciting trial attempts, which is how do I get people to try and do stuff, not to recite information?
Because once they get in the real world, it has very little to do with reciting information.
And when information is available at your fingertips in real time and personalized, that skill is almost nothing.